= kisskh.ca =
[Subtitles in the making and will be available soon]
The characters, behavior, and location of the drama
[KNOT Love Contract]
organizations, occupations,
and various incidents
are fictitious, only for entertainment.
They have no intention to guide
or encourage anything in the drama.
Please watch it rationally.
M flow ENTERTAINMENT
You're worth my pursuit
Do you love me or not?
A little kiss once lingered on my lips
Baby, I want you to belong to me
Please give me some response
A signal of love
Make my world beautiful again
With bright eyes
Hold my hand tightly
Don't you think I belong to you? ♪
But I'm always influenced by others
You look like a little fool
In the end, you must lose
We must lose
We're destined to lose
[KNOT Love Contract]
[Previously]
How dare you betray our family?
The one who sold the news about our family
has no right to scold me.
Why are you
so nervous?
What's going on?
Get out of here!
Abandon!
I missed the first shot.
but I aimed at it.
Brother, are you hurt badly?
I'm far away from my heart, little hero.
Are you okay?
Brother.
How long are we going to stay here?
I can't reach anyone.
My phone is broken.
And your phone?
It's in Nakan's car.
What?
Why am I so unlucky?
You haven't treated your wound yet.
Can you use socks?
Use this to make do.
Does it hurt?
Phasa.
If you were gentle,
I won't feel any pain.
You're still joking when it hurts like this?
If I didn't tease you,
I was afraid you would cry.
I saw you get shot.
Who wouldn't be afraid?
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
It's not your fault.
Phasa.
Thank you.
I don't want anything to happen to you.
I'm just afraid of being a widow.
Are you feeling better now?
I just scratched my arm.
Besides, the bullet wasn't in her body.
Alpha's recovery is fast.
Besides, I'm True Alpha.
This wound...
is nothing.
But you bled a lot just now.
You're really amazing today.
Without you,
I wouldn't have been able to sit here.
I didn't think that much.
I didn't expect
that Sangnua is the mastermind.
he was so weak
he made everyone lower their guard.
In the end, he lied to all of us.
I gave Tim and Saanguya a chance.
I thought kindness could change someone.
But the more I gave them the chance, the more I helped them.
But it's not your fault.
If a person is determined to betray,
no matter how much you pay,
you'll still be blamed.
Thank you.
You made me see a lot.
I wonder
went to Angsa?
I'm worried too.
I don't know what's going on over there.
I don't want to stay here anymore.
I really want to leave.
Those kids will be fine.
They're smart and strong.
Everything will be over soon.
Yes.
Everyone is amazing.
They're so good that they can help you.
Don't carry it alone anymore.
You don't have to be so tired
Including you?
Yes.
I'll be with you.
You took everything from me.
and made me into OMEGA.
I had to hide
and live like an invisible person.
That's why I called Tim
to destroy you.
and send you to hell.
Just like my family did.
Do you like this feeling?
Luckily,
Tim always treats me as his brother.
No matter what I ask him to do,
he will do
Anything.
Even if
his ex,
and he did the same.
But of course, you don't have to stand up and talk.
Especially you, the spoiled Young Master Beata.
My parents and Alpha An OMEGA
grew up in a warm family.
Do you know how I grew up?
I can only steal things
with information.
and exchange everything
to exchange everything
to survive.
Isn't it pitiful?
The source of all this
is your family.
It's you.
The Devoting Family.
You ruined my family
You ruined my family and my dad.
I don't know how you found out,
but everything you know is wrong.
Saanguya.
Your family
has always been helping you.
My dad helped you bid for the project.
He also suggested to mortgage the land
so that you can circulate funds.
Your family cheated our family.
Because your family
has been thinking about my dad's land.
Why do we need your land?
Since we've been friends for generations,
my dad has been helping you.
But your family
turned to another family
and sold our secrets.
just to protect ourselves.
In the end, you took the wrong side
and lost everything.
Impossible.
You're lying.
If you don't believe me,
go to Amintra's house.
Before your father died,
before he died?
before he was hunted?
Impossible.
What am I doing
is nothing.
I've been wearing a mask
and lied to myself.
Was I always wrong?
Then why did you make me
I was born OMEGA.
Why did you make me experience all this?
Why?
Brother.
What are you doing?
Nakkin, calm down.
Get lost. Stay out of this.
Brother!
NAKIN.
NAKHIn.
NAKHIN
Sangnouea.
Nanakin.
Someone said that revenge is never over.
But that wasn't for me.
That's why I'm here to settle this.
Saanguya.
From now on,
with your hatred.
Natch.
What did you do?
You scared me today.
Me?
Yes.
He shot Tim down.
I didn’t expect OMEGA to be so fierce.
He shot you first.
Of course I'm angry for you.
You're so protective of me.
He hurt you.
Phasa.
Yes?
You'll stay by my side tonight.
You took care of me and worried about me.
Do you have something to tell me?
No.
Really?
Yes.
Your hands are trembling and your tears are about to fall.
It has nothing to do with me.
You started making fun of me as soon as you woke up.
I'm just asking. Or are you afraid to answer?
Who doesn't dare to answer?
Then tell me
how do you feel about me?
How can you say it at a time like this?
Why can't I?
I...
Which word is stuck?
Worried, missing, or...
love
♪Wu♪
Are you okay?
Thank you
♪It keeps repeating♪
Trapped in the same place
My heart
It's always the same
Trapped in
In the time when I can't find the exit
When I close my eyes, it's all you ♪
I'm bound by your figure and drowned in the dream
I'm trapped and have nowhere to run
Only your words
We love each other
But I don't know whether it's true or not ♪
Fate
Why is it so cruel
Why did it have to be me
I only see you in my eyes
You
What's wrong?
Is it that hard to say?
♪Being trapped♪
Yeah, it's really hard
In the time when we can't find the exit
It's not that hard
I'm bound by your shadow and immersed in my dream
You go first
♪Fall in love♪
Okay
♪ I have nowhere to run ♪ Only your words
Listen
We love each other
Love
But I don't know whether it's true or not ♪
♪Wu♪
See? It's not hard at all
Of course it's not hard for you.
Let me teach you.
Follow me.
Love
When I close my eyes, it's all you
♪ All because of you, bound by your figure ♪ Drowned in the dream
Next
You
♪ I’m trapped, I have nowhere to run ♪ Only your words
Say it together now
♪We love each other♪
But I don't know whether it's true or not ♪
I forgot
When I close my eyes, it's all you
Say it
I'm bound by your shadow and drowned in the dream
Love you
I'm trapped and have nowhere to run
Only your words say we love each other ♪
So cute
♪  But I don’t know whether it’s true or not♪ ♪
Next.
Are you not done yet?
I want to hear the whole story.
Tell me who you love.
I love you.
Who do you love?
I love Nakhun.
Good. Remember.
From now on, you can only say this to me.
You're so cunning.
Why?
You don't like it?
I didn't say I don't like it.
I'll take that as a yes.
Promise what?
You promised me to receive your reward after your confession.
I...
Love.
Phasa.
I love Phasa.
Now,
do you remember the love I said?
I will never forget
I'll never forget it.
Doesn't your wound hurt?
No.
Phasa.
I think the lock is locked.
What?
Ah!
Brother, you really locked it.
Mr. Nakhun.
Mr. Phasa.
Are you all right?
How is it?
Silla, AI.
We're fine.
Nankhun got shot.
What?
Then we need to get out of here quickly.
Or the wound will get infected.
AI, Sila, come and help.
OK. OK.
Go get the car.
You just asked
why Mr. Narat's men
find that place?
Actually, Old Master
sent someone to look for Pule. OMEGA.
They've been investigating
all the hospital database you've been to.
Then I got personal information from the old hospital.
So I found your old apartment address.
But I moved out a long time ago.
Yes, but they never gave up.
When you went back to the old apartment
at the old apartment that day,
someone saw your car,
and installed a GPS tracker.
As soon as GPS made a move,
they went all the way there.
In fact, we have long suspected
that you're PureOmega.
That's why I rushed over to save you.
I'm sorry.
I failed to protect you.
It's okay.
I understand.
But Mr. Phasa,
you look pale.
You're injured too.
Don't you want the doctor to take a look?
I'm fine.
I want to wait for Brother Nakhun
to treat his wound first.
I just want to make sure he's safe.
to make sure he's safe.
Mr. Phasa.
Phasa.
Hello, Mr. Phasa.
Mr. Phasa.
Nurse!
Phasa!
Someone fainted.
I'll call someone over.
Okay, please hurry up.
Phasa.
Dad.
Son, are you hurt anywhere?
No, I'm fine.
Where's Nakhun?
Where is he?
Are you talking about Alpha who bit you?
I'll take care of him now.
Dad.
What's wrong, kid?
He bit you.
and hurt you like this.
Do you want me to sit back and watch?
No, Dad.
Don't go.
Why?
You're OMEGA.
He made a contract with you.
Are you going to let Alpha
be okay?
But he didn't.
Why are you still defending him?
I just want to know if he's safe.
He did this to you.
He was the first person you asked when you woke up.
Dad.
Have a good rest.
But this matter...
Brother Nakhun.
Hello.
How are you?
It doesn't hurt at all.
It's just a minor injury.
I'm here
to apologize.
Apologize for biting Phasa.
I really didn't want this to happen.
At that time,
I couldn't control my instinct.
You can't control yourself?
Yes.
You can't even control yourself.
But my son has made a contract with you.
Dad.
What do you want me to think?
Do you want me to take this as an accident?
Then where is Saanguya now?
[In the next episode]
That's not important.
The real headache is the future trouble.
I'll take full responsibility.
Mom, have you really decided?
I've already decided.
I finally made up my mind today.
Phasa.
[Henry] [MEDICAL CENTER]
Why is she Phatsa?
Are you sure?
What you just said
not to take my son away.
What if something happens to Phasa?
Where's Phasa?
Wasn't he here just now?
How could you let them take my wife?
What kind of bodyguard are you?
I left those beautiful memories
I thought we were meant to be
But I know
that's not the reality
I tried my best to stop you from leaving
But the broken love has long been broken
Because I always believe you will stay
I'm willing to give up everything for you
We should have had the best future
But there will be no result
Only tears are left
Only memories are left
How many more times do I have to hurt to understand
How long do I have to cry
My heart tells me to let go
If I leave one day
you probably won't feel anything
Just like I've never existed
It really hurts
I have to admit that I really miss you
If there's still a little love left
you won't choose to leave
♪ But I don't know what's the point of persistence ♪
Our mouths and hearts always turn against each other
No matter how painful my heart is I have to admit
I really miss you
In fact, I understand But I never thought about accepting it
We should have had the best future
But there will be no result Only tears are left
Only memories are left
How many more times do I have to hurt to understand
How long do I have to cry
My heart tells me to let go
If one day
I leave
You probably won't feel anything
Just like I never existed
I keep in those beautiful memories
I thought we were meant to be
♪I have to admit♪
It really hurts
I have to admit
I really miss you. If one day ♪
If I leave
You probably won't feel anything
Just like I've never existed